

BRIEFLY ABOUT YOURSELF

Hello! I am a PHP and Laravel developer, I am twenty-five years old, I live in the city of Lviv. I also have a higher engineering education!

Experience with both native PHP/SQL/JS and frameworks. Laravel/mySQL/Redis/Vue. The total freelance+commercial experience is - 1 year.

Ready to learn and develop further!:)

TECH SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3 (SASS/SCSS)
- PHP 7.3+ / MySQL / Laravel
- JavaScript ES6+ / Vue.js
- REST API / AJAX/ OOP
- Gulp / Webpack / Vite
- Bootstrap / Tailwind CSS / jQuery
- GIT version control

MY CONTACTS

Phone (mobile): +38 (067) 212-88-19 Email: andreilevitsky23@gmail.com Website: www.andrewlev.biz.ua

Linkedin: @andrewlev23 GitHub: @Andrewlevvv23 Telegram: @Andrew_levvv



LANGUAGE SKILLS

Ukrainian - native English - Pre-Intermediate

ANDREW LEVYTSKYI

WEB DEVELOPER

25 years old

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

Kyiv University of Construction and Architecture

Master's degree | Kyiv (2014-2019)

-Graduated from the Kyiv National Construction University with a degree in civil engineering with honors, before that he graduated from a college in the city of Sevastopol.

Udemy programming courses

Graduate student | Kyiv and Iviv (2021-2022)

- For almost 2 years now, I have been actively taking full-stack courses on the Udemy educational platform, YouTube and documentation. Teachers like Laravel Daily and Dr. Angela Y. In total, I spent more than 1100+ hours studying and practicing, and it paid off!

EXPERIENCE

BIM design engineer

'KAN Development' | Kyiv (02.2019 - 02.2022)

-Development of project documentation, drawing, communication with clients, work with the AutoCAD program

Junior Full-Stack Developer

Freelancing jobs | Kyiv (08.2022 - 02.2023)

- Development of business cards and landing pages for your friends and acquaintances. Also work on your pet projects both in native PHP/SQL/JS and Laravel/Redis/MySQL/Vue.js

Junior Backend Developer

'SK-Group EU' | Lviv (04.2023 - 07.2023)

- Product development for automation of warehouses and logistics using native PHP/MySQL/JQuery. Extension and editing of existing functionality, practice with a large volume of data in the database and a large amount of logic in the program itself

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Made more than ten projects using technologies: HTML/SCSS/Bootstrap/PHP 8+/Vue/MySQL/Laravel 10 All of them are available for viewing on my repository: https://github.com/Andrewlevvv23

Or from links on my personal website, a summary I made from scratch before publishing on hosting: https://andrewlev.biz.ua/

